[
  {

    "index": 0,

    "question": "Video Player , Blue Color icon with while design , allow to Zoom Video like pics",

    "answer": "mx player"

  },

  {

    "index": 1,

    "question": "chatting app , Green & white icon , Used by 5bilion people  ",

    "answer": "whatsapp"

  },

  {

    "index": 2,

    "question": "Social Media Platform , watch Video , That is You",

    "answer": "youtube"

  },

{

    "index": 3,

    "question": "Red Yellow white purple icon , Weight is Gram , where you shoot With filter , Process is Instant",

    "answer": "instagram"

  },

{

    "index": 4,

    "question": "i am Blue & White , i am Book , You can Upload Your Face on me",

    "answer": "facebook"

  },

{

    "index": 5,

    "question": "Weight in Gram , White icon , Tell me Name",

    "answer": "talegram"

  },

  {

    "index": 6,

    "question": "king of Board game , 4 player Board Game , Made in india Game , Gametion Technology Made This",

    "answer": "ludo king"

  },

  {

    "index": 7,

    "question": "Browser , 4 Colour Icon , Liked By Most People",

    "answer": "Chrome"

  },

  {

    "index": 8,

    "question": "Allow You To Click Pic , AI Blur Images",

    "answer": "camera"

  },

  {

    "index": 9,

    "question": "Manage Preferences , INBUILT in every device, ",

    "answer": "setting"

  },

  {

    "index": 10,

    "question": "Virtual Storage 15gb free , Trusted Provider",

    "answer": "google drive"

  },

  {

    "index": 11,

    "question": "Academy Where You Study Virtually , Online Lecture , Online Video on YT , Educational App",

    "answer": "unacademy"

  },

  {

    "index": 12,

    "question": "Study with 2 Teacher Advantage ðŸ˜‚ but Virtualy , Brand Embracing Salman Khan",

    "answer": "byju's"

  },

  {

    "index": 13,

    "question": "Cart where Add Any thing like U flip Your Phone , Shopping app ",

    "answer": "flipkart"

  }

  

]